

Anastasiia Onyshchenko Front-end Developer

Contacts +380509648346 anastasiya.onishchenk@gmail.com nastjaonishenko

Summary

I am a Front-End developer with more than 4 years of experience. I have strong knowledge of web development, optimizing websites and single-page applications. Also I have a good experience in teamwork and in UI/UX design.

Major Skills

- React
- Redux
- React Hooks
- Rest API
- React Router
- **JavaScript**
- ¡Query/¡Query UI
- HTML
- CSS
- Sass/SCSS/Less

Other Skills

Front-End: ES5/ES6, Bootstrap 2/3/4,

Redux, Webpack Back-End: PHP, Ruby

Platform: Wordpress, Shopify, OpenCart Additional: Zeplin, Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop/Sketch, Git, Email design features, Google services (Fonts, Hosted Libraries, Analytics)

Education, Master's degree

2020 - 2021

National Technical University 'Kharkiv Polytechnic Institute', Department of Software Engineering

2016 - 2020

Kharkiv National University of Economics, Department of Economical cybernetics

Professional Experience

Oct 2022 - now Agile Fuel

Build scalable, high-quality software products that meet the needs of end-users and stakeholders.

Apr 2018 - 2022 Aimprosoft

Build websites and single-page applications that are responsive and usable. Development of websites, landing pages, and electronic direct mail campaigns.

Feb 2016 - Apr 2018 **Vilmate**

Development of websites on WordPress and OpenCart platforms, landing pages, and electronic direct mail campaigns.

Major Projects

Content Scheduling Platform

a platform marketplace to allow advertisers, media agencies and exhibitors to plan campaigns, choose to target content to specific theatres, schedule any kind of content at the theatres for playback.

Role: Front-End Developer

Responsibilities: Develop and implement user interface with React.js, Troubleshoot and debug code issues Create and maintain technical documentation, Create reusable components, Work with data from API

Platform: Node is

Technologies: React, Redux, React Router, Hooks, Context, Npm, Yarn

Tools: IntelliJ IDEA, Git Team size: 5-7

Application For Sharing, Uploading, Saving And Purchasing

STYLES - The web-application is created for sharing, uploading, saving and purchasing styles. Styles consist of items that could be purchased by users on Amazon.com.

Role: Front-End Developer Responsibilities:

Creating custom React components Responsive styles for components Adding actions to components Working with data from API

Platform: Node.js Databases: MySQL Technologies: npm React, Redux, Webpack SCSS Third parties: JWT, Zoho Sales IQ

Tools: IntelliJ IDEA, Git Team size: 3-5

Team Chat For Company

This project is a collaboration hub that brings the right people, information, and tools together to get work done in the company. The chat allows you to define a unique account, fill out your profile, manage notification settings. This chat makes it simple to follow conversations or find important information in an easily searchable archive. Target environments: WEB, Desktop, iOS ad Android applications.

Role: Front-End Developer

Responsibilities: Creating custom React components

Responsive styles for components

Adding actions to components, Working with data from API

Platform: Web Databases: MySQL Technologies: React, Redux, SASS, SCSS,

Third parties: Firebase Tools: IntelliJ IDEA, Git Team size: 6 - 11

Business Card Site For Healthcare Production

This site is abusiness card. It was founded to transform the healthcare industry with effective solutions for everyone: health conscious users, patients, doctors and healthcare providers.

Role: Front-End Developer Responsibilities: Creating and support template for WordPress

Creating and support template for Zendesk

Developing responsive styles

Installation and configuration WordPress plugins Developing styles for WordPress plugins Using Bootstrap library for design features

Platform: WordPress, Zendesk

Databases: MvSOL

Technologies: HTML, CSS, SCSS, jQuery, Bootstrap, PHP, Grunt, GA tools, Liquid Tools: IntelliJ IDEA, Git, PixelPerfect, PHP Storm,

Adobe Illustrator Team size: 3 - 4

Healthcare Shopify Shops

 $this \, e\text{-}Commerce \, project \, is \, created \, for \, selling \, healthcare \, electronic \, we arable \, devices. \, It \, consists \, of \, 7 \, shops \, that \, are \, devices \, devic$ developed on the Shopify platform. Each shop is used for a specific place and is multilanguage. The shop proposes 3 products: a device for taking control of your heart health; a smart scale; a wearable ECG. (which is available for each location except the US). The project has Shopify plus, so we have the opportunity to work on some challenging and interesting tasks with checkout.

Role: Front-End Developer Responsibilities:

Support template for Shopify

Developing layouts for custom Shopify component Developing styles for default Shopify component

Developing an adaptive site view

Platform: Shopify Plus

Technologies: Ruby Liquid, scss, js

Third parties: Zendesk

Tools: IntelliJ IDEA, Theme Kit, PixelPerfect,

Sketch Team size: 1 - 4